Your total is 3200 yen.
전부 3,200엔입니다
Why don't they have the volume two of the grimoire?
왜 마법서 하권이 없지?
I bought that volume one at a used book store.
상권을 헌책방에서 샀어
You're just looking in the wrong place.
네가 엉뚱한 곳에서 찾는 거야
I'm happy with my purchase.
난 이걸 사서 기분 좋다
It's Yurine.
유리네다
DROPKICK ON MY DEVIL! ANIMATED SERIES TO START
'사신짱 드롭킥 애니 시작'
USING GRIMOIRE FROM USED BOOK STORE TO PERFORM CONJURATION.
'중고 서점에서 산 마법서로 주문을 외우다'
It's true...
사실인데...
Aren't you hungry?
배고프니?
Let's grab a bite somewhere.
먹으러 가자
What do you want?
뭐 먹고 싶니?
Yurine!
유리네!
What? Me?
나? 뭐?
I wanna go to Jiro.
난 지로에 가고 싶어
Let's go to Jiro.
지로로 가자
Then why ask in the first place?
그럼 애초에 왜 물은 거야?
What's Jiro, anyway?
그런데 지로가 뭐지?
And... is it true?
그리고... 이거 사실인가?
We're an anime series?
우리가 애니 시리즈라고?
Get with it, girl!
정신 차려, 아가씨!
Won’t leave
떠나려면
without a dropkick on her!
저 애에게 드롭킥을 날려야 해
Zazas Zazas Nasatanada Zazas
자자스 자자스 나사타나다 자자스
-She summoned me, the evil god. -Evil god!
- 저 애가 소환한 난 악마다 - 악마다!
-I gotta kill her or else -What?
저 애를 죽이지 않으면 뭐?
-I can’t go back to Hell! -Sister...
지옥에 갈 수가 없어 자매여...
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Life next to death, I combat with my chainsaw!
그래! 그래! 그래! 죽음과 살기 위해, 전기톱으로 싸워야지!
If you go too far,
네가 막 나가면
I’ll slice you up completely!
널 완전히 썰어버릴 거야!
Your halo! Must get it back!
네 후광을 반드시 되찾아야지!
-Never miss a chance -Hey, seriously?
기회를 절대 놓치지 마 정말 그럴 거야?
-To attack her from behind! -You’re so mean.
뒤에서 공격하려고? 넌 못됐어
I’ll never give up.
난 절대 포기 안 해
Yurine, you’re off your guard!
유리네, 방심하고 있군!
Now! Time to finish you with the Royal Copenhagen!
지금이다! 로열코펜하겐으로 끝내주지!
Huh? What? I missed...
어, 뭐지? 실패다...
Can’t leave Earth
지구를 떠나려면
without a dropkick on her!
저 애에게 드롭킥을 날려야 해
But until then,
하지만 그때까진
-let’s all have fun together! -Yeah!
모두 같이 놀자! 신난다!
KITCHEN JIRO
'지로 키친'
Welcome.
어서 오세요
You always order the fried minced meat with fried fish plate.
넌 항상 멘치가스와 생선가스만 주문하더라?
It's my favorite! And look who's talking.
제일 좋아하는 거니까 그러는 너는?
You always get the scallop croquette plate.
너도 항상 가리비 크로켓만 먹잖아
Well, yeah, it's my favorite.
그래 내가 제일 좋아하는 거야
I want a bite of that.
나도 한 입 먹어볼게
No way.
안 돼
I don't believe in sharing or letting people try my food.
내 음식을 다른 사람하고 나눠 먹거나 맛보게 하는 거 안 해
Just be happy with what you ordered.
네가 주문한 음식만 맛있게 먹어
Sorry, never mind.
미안, 실례했어
I can't finish the rice.
밥을 다 못 먹겠다
Jashin-chan, eat the rest.
사신짱, 남은 거 먹어
Okay...
그래...
She just contradicted herself.
자기가 방금 안 한다고 해놓고
But, if I say anything she'll get mad. I'll just let it slide...
하지만 뭐라고 하면 화내겠지 그냥 내버려 두자
That was delicious.
아주 맛있었다
Excuse me. I'd like to order the fried minced meat lunch set.
여기요, 멘치가스 도시락 하나 주세요
Right away!
바로 나갑니다!
What are you gonna do with that?
그거 왜 시킨 거야?
Is it for dinner?
저녁에 먹으려고?
I need to stop by somewhere.
잠깐 들를 데가 있어
Pekola, are you here? I got food for you.
페코라, 있니? 내가 음식 가져 왔어
Why take care of that fallen angel?
저 타락한 천사를 왜 돌보는 거지?
Pekola?
페코라?
I'm not Pekola.
난 페코라가 아니다
Whoops, wrong one.
이런, 잘못 찾아 왔네요
Pekola's over there.
페코라는 저기 있어
I see. Thank you.
네, 고맙습니다
The witch and her familiar spirit. What do you want?
마녀하고 그 마귀야 왜 온 거야?
How rude.
아주 버릇이 없군
I could kill you if I wanted to.
마음만 먹으면 널 죽일 수 있어
Stop! Since I lost my halo not only am I weak,
하지 마! 후광을 잃어버려서 힘이 약해진 데다
I'm also starving to death. I can barely move.
배가 고파 죽을 것 같아서 꼼짝도 못 해
That's why I brought you this.
그래서 이걸 가져온 거야
A fried minced meat lunch set?
멘치가스 도시락?
For me...?
날 위해서...?
No! As an angel, I can't accept food from a witch!
안 돼! 난 천사야 마녀가 주는 음식은 못 받아
Please go home.
제발 가줘
Just so you know, I'm not a witch.
알려줄 게 있는데 난 마녀가 아니야
Do what you want.
마음대로 해
I'll just leave this here.
여기다 두고 갈게
Let's go, Jashin-chan.
사신짱, 가자
Okay.
그래
I want it so bad!
정말 먹고 싶다!
No! I can't!
안 돼! 난 못 해!
What angel accepts food from a witch?
천사가 어떻게 마녀가 주는 음식을 받아?
But, I can't just let the food go to waste either.
하지만 음식을 버릴 수도 없잖아?
Never mind the witch,
마녀는 신경 쓰지 말자
wouldn't it be disrespectful to the chef if I didn't eat it?
내가 먹지 않으면 요리사를 무시하는 거지
Right! I'll eat it for the chef!
그래! 요리사를 위해서 먹는 거다
Bon appetit!
맛있게 드세요!
THIS IS PEKOLA'S IMAGINATION
'페코라의 상상이다'
All right! Let's eat!
좋아! 먹자!
Smells so good...
냄새가 너무 좋다...
What are you doing here?
넌 여기서 뭐 해?
Since you weren't gonna eat it, thought I'd eat it for you.
넌 안 먹을 거니까 내가 대신 먹어주는 거야
Didn't want to waste it!
음식을 버리기 싫어서
What? Did you want to eat it?
왜? 먹으려던 거야?
Of course not.
당연히 아니지
Good.
잘됐군
That was the last bite.
다 먹었거든
So juicy and delicious!
너무 촉촉하고 맛있다!
That meat was to die for! I know, I'm not the best food reporter...
고기 맛이 끝내준다! 내가 맛 설명을 잘하는 사람은 아니지만
All done! Here, throw this away.
다 먹었으니까 받아서 갖다 버려
I'm so satisfied!
정말 기분 좋다!
Jeez, my stomach's a bottomless pit.
이런, 내 배는 아무리 채워도 끝이 없어
That's okay.
그래도 괜찮아
I was able to protect my dignity as an angel.
천사의 품위는 지킨 거야
I'll drink some water and go to bed.
물이나 마시고 자야겠다
Patrasche, I'm tired now.
파트라슈, 난 피곤해
HOURS LATER
'몇 시간 후'
You disappeared on the way back home.
넌 집에 오는 길에 사라졌지
Don't tell me you went back and ate Pekola's food.
다시 돌아가서 페코라의 음식을 먹은 건 아니겠지?
No. I didn't eat it.
아니야, 안 먹었어
-Are you sure? -Yeah!
- 진짜니? - 네!
If you don't tell me the truth...
사실대로 말 안 하면
I'll mince your arm into pieces.
네 팔을 갈아버릴 거다
Yeah! I ate it! I ate it!
그래, 먹었다! 먹었어!
We'll serve fried Jashin-chan meat for dinner tonight.
오늘 저녁은 사신짱 멘치가스다
PLEASE WAIT A MOMENT
'잠시만 기다리세요'
I'm gonna go to Jiro to get Pekola some food again.
난 지로로 가서 페코라에게 줄 음식을 살 거야
So, restore your arm and clean up the mess. Okay?
그러니까 팔을 재생하고 말끔히 청소해
Damn it.
제기랄
I even told her the truth.
사실대로 다 털어놨는데
Damn it!
젠장!
PIPING HOT FRIED MINCED MEAT
'따끈따끈한 멘치가스'
Bless the witch!
마녀에게 축복을 내리소서!
Hello!
안녕!
I brought something cool from Hell for you.
지옥에서 너한테 주려고 아주 멋진 걸 가져왔어
Check out the Mandragora doll!
만드라고라 인형이다
Also known as the mandrake.
맨드레이크라고도 하죠
Legend says anyone who pulls them out
전설에선 이걸 뽑은 사람은
and hears their screams goes mad and dies!
비명을 듣고 미쳐서 죽는다고 합니다
You press the stomach to hear its death scream.
배를 누르면 죽음의 비명을 들을 수 있어
Listen.
들어 봐
That's freaky.
징그럽다
That's so metal.
메탈 음악 같네
So lame.
한심하군
-Like it? -Yup.
- 맘에 들어? - 응
Good. The Mandragora's happy too.
좋다 만드라고라도 행복하대
Jashin-chan is such a sleaze.
사신짱은 아주 비열한데
But her friends, Medusa and Minos, are so nice.
쟤 친구인 메두사와 미노스는 정말 착해
Even though Jashin-chan's such a jerk.
저렇게 못된 사신짱을 상대해 주다니
She's not even my friend anyway.
쟨 내 친구가 아니야
Hey, that's not nice.
섭섭하다
What?
뭐?
Do you have any idea how many times I got hurt because of you?
너 때문에 내가 얼마나 많이 다쳤는지 알아?
-I'll push you, Jashin-chan! -What?
- 내가 밀어줄게, 사신짱 - 응?
Here you go!
간다!
Let's play some more!
조금만 더 놀자
Leave me alone.
귀찮게 하지 마
Come on, let's go!
자, 간다!
What's going on?
왜 그러는 거야?
I dislocated my back...
내 등 뼈가 탈구됐어...
I apologized right then and there. It wasn't on purpose either.
그때 바로 사과했어 일부러 그런 것도 아니잖아
That's not the point!
그게 중요한 게 아니지!
You gotta be more careful!
더 조심했어야지!
You meathead!
이 바보야!
What? This is all because you're so weak!
뭐라고? 네가 너무 약한 게 문제다
What? I'm not weak! Try me!
뭐? 내가 왜 약해? 덤벼 봐!
Let's do it.
좋다
I'll show you!
본때를 보여주지
Take this! Jashin-chan Dropkick!
받아라! 사신짱 드롭킥이다
The animation!
애니메이션!
Go!
간다!
You think I'm scared of that?
내가 겁낼 줄 알고?
Hey, Mandragora...
이봐, 만드라고라
NO RESPONSE. IT'S PROBABLY DEAD.
'반응 없음 사망으로 추정'
That was its real death scream.
정말 죽음의 비명이었네
Oh, well.
괜찮아
It was freaky anyway.
징그러웠거든
Right, Yurine?
그렇지, 유리네?
I was getting pretty attached to it.
내가 매우 좋아하던 거다
Yurine?
유리네?
Well, I gotta go deliver the evening paper. See you later.
난 석간신문 배달하러 가야 해 나중에 보자
Minos, you traitor!
미노스, 이 배신자!
The death scream...
그 죽음의 비명이
I thought it was pretty cute.
아주 귀엽다고 생각했지
It's a rare toy too.
아주 희귀한 장난감이었어
Need I say more?
말 안 해도 알지?
There we go.
됐다
Oh, come on. Give me a better scream.
자, 비명을 더 질러야지
The Mandragora's death scream was way better than that.
만드라고라의 죽음의 비명이 훨씬 더 좋다
Stop... I can't do it...
하지 마... 난 못 해
Scream loud and clear.
더 크게 잘 들리게 비명을 질러
No matter how hard I work,
아무리 열심히 노력해도
life just gets harder and harder.
사는 게 점점 더 힘들다
I'll just stare at my hand.
그저 손 하나만 지켜봐야겠다
Working is fun!
일하는 건 즐겁다!
You work, you lose.
넌 일하니까 진 거야
I'll just stare at my hand.
난 내 손만 볼 거야
Good morning, mascot of India.
안녕, 인도의 마스코트야
How's the new room, Totem Pole?
새 방이 마음에 드니, 장승아?
Bus-tine.
버스 표지판아
It took a lot of effort to get you here.
널 데려오느라고 아주 힘들었어
I love how the bus schedule is posted right there.
버스 시간표가 이렇게 붙어 있는 게 너무 좋아
You're my precious babies.
너희는 나의 소중한 아가들이다
I just need Orochimaru to complete my collection.
오로치마루만 있으면 내 수집이 완성될 텐데
Shoot! I'm gonna be late!
이런, 지각하겠다!
I, Mei Tachibana, the super cop of the Banzaibashi Police will protect this land from all evil!
나, 타치바나 메이는 반자이바시 슈퍼 경찰로 모든 악마로부터 이 땅을 수호한다!
I must stay on high alert for weirdos while I'm on patrol.
이상한 인간들이 있으니 순찰할 땐 경계 태세를 유지해야 해
Are you okay?
괜찮아요?
I'm fine.
괜찮습니다
I just have a weak body.
몸이 약해서 그래요
Excuse me.
실례합니다
She had such a cute voice.
목소리가 아주 귀엽다
All clear.
문제 해결
Excuse me, sir.
실례합니다, 선생님
Are you interested in woodblock prints?
목판화에 관심이 있나요?
Woodblock prints?
목판화요?
They're a bit pricey, but you can pay in installments.
조금 비싸지만 할부로 내시면 돼요
It'll be a good investment for your future.
미래를 위한 좋은 투자가 될 겁니다
Let me show you.
제가 보여드릴게요
Sure.
좋아요
-I'll just take a look. -One silkscreen please!
- 한번 보죠 - 실크스크린 하나요!
GALLERY
'화랑'
NEGOTIATING
'상담 중'
Yup, all clear.
그래, 이상 무
How wonderful!
아주 멋져요!
I love his form and his wacky Halloween-ish outfit.
이 분 자세도 엽기 핼러윈 복장 같은 것도 다 좋다
He's so beautiful, I'm tearing up.
너무 아름다워서 눈물이 난다
I'm going to take him home.
집으로 데려가야지
Here we go.
가죠
Excuse me.
실례합니다
Is there a problem with that figure?
그 상에 문제가 있나요?
Did someone plant a bomb on it?
누가 폭탄을 심었어요?
No, I'm taking him home because he's so cute.
아니요 너무 예뻐서 집에 데려가려고요
He wants to go home with me too, right?
이분도 나랑 같이 집에 가고 싶대요, 그렇죠?
"Yes, I do."
"네, 그래요"
See?
봤죠?
What a freak.
정말 돌았군
I better call the police.
경찰을 불러야겠다
But wait, is she a cop? I'm so confused.
잠깐, 저 여자가 경찰이야? 어떻게 하지?
I'm just a part-timer.
난 그저 아르바이트생이잖아
What am I supposed to do?
어떻게 하면 좋지?
Let's go!
같이 가요!
Wait! You can't take our mascot!
이봐요 마스코트를 가져가면 안 돼요!
-Did you just touch my butt? -What?
- 내 엉덩이를 만졌어요? - 뭐요?
He's a pervert! Someone call the cops! Help!
이 사람 변태예요! 경찰을 불러줘요! 도와주세요
I didn't touch you!
안 만졌어요!
I'm taking him home.
이 사람을 데려갈 거예요
Let go, you freak.
놔, 이 괴물아
-It's that freak from the other day. -This belongs to the shop.
- 저번에 봤던 그 괴물이다 - 이건 가게 거야
I was meeting up with Medusa, but I can't let her see me.
메두사와 만나기로 했는데 저 여자가 날 보면 안 돼
Jashin-chan!
사신짱!
Jashin-chan? Orochimaru!
사신짱? 오로치마루다!
Were you waiting for a while?
한참 기다렸니?
I bought you some chicken.
닭고기를 사 왔어
What's wrong?
왜 그래?
Forget this! I want Orochimaru!
이건 됐어 난 오로치마루를 가질 거야
Damn it! She saw me!
젠장! 저 여자가 날 봤다
Orochimaru! Wait, my dear!
오로치마루 기다려, 내 사랑!
I have to get away from her!
저 여자에게 잡히면 안 돼
Jeez, slow down!
천천히 가!
What's going on?
왜 그러는 거야?
Did you do something?
너 무슨 짓을 저질렀니?
You have to make up for your crimes.
죄를 지었으면 보상을 해야 해
Shut up!
시끄러워!
Orochimaru!
오로치마루!
Bull's-eye!
명중이다!
Jashin-chan! Are you okay?
사신짱, 괜찮아?
Not at all.
전혀
I LOVE OROCHIMARU
'오로치마루를 사랑한다'
Gotcha!
잡았다!
Oh, Orochimaru.
오로치마루
So beautiful... So cute...
너무 아름답고... 너무 귀여워
So smooth.
매우 부드럽다
Stop it!
하지 마!
Orochimaru's the best!
오로치마루가 최고다!
Time for our celebratory selfie!
셀피 타임이다!
Stop! I can't!
하지 마! 난 못 해!
JASHIN-CHAN DOUBLE PEACE
'사신짱, 평화의 V 사인 2개'
Nice shot!
나이스 샷!
Everything looks delicious.
다 맛있어 보인다
Pekola, don't forget about dessert.
페코라, 디저트도 꼭 드세요!
Have some nectar too.
과즙 주스도요
ANGEL IN TRAINING
'수습 천사'
This is so much food.
음식이 너무 많아
Steak, onion soup...
스테이크, 양파 수프...
Parfait, cake, unleavened bread...
파르페, 케이크 무효모빵
Bagna cauda...
바냐 카우다
-Tiramisu... -Hey!
- 티라미수 - 어이!
-Fried minced meat... -Hey, wake up!
- 멘치가스... - 이봐, 정신 차려!
I'm talking to you, part-timer!
아르바이트생, 너 말이야!
Me?
저요?
You're here to work.
여긴 일하는 곳이야
Don't daydream while you're on the clock.
근무 중에 공상하지 마!
Come on, move it.
빨리, 움직여
Why do I get treated like this?
왜 내가 이런 대접을 받아야 하지?
I was an angel, you know?
난 천사야, 알아?
We're forced to climb up the stairs with heavy loads on our backs.
무거운 짐을 등에 지고 계단을 올라가게 한다
Are we building a pyramid or something?
피라미드 같은 거라도 짓는 건가?
We climb up the stairs and go back down in an elevator.
계단으로 올라가고 엘리베이터로 내려간다
How much longer will I last?
난 얼마나 더 버틸 수 있을까?
For 400 yen per hour?
시간당 400엔이라고?
Why is it so low?
왜 시급이 낮지?
Isn't Tokyo's minimum wage 958 yen?
도쿄 최저 시급은 958엔이잖아
But, I have to do this to survive.
하지만 살기 위해선 해야 한다
No other place would hire me without a background check.
신원 조사 안 하고 날 써줄 곳은 여기밖에 없어
There. That was heavy.
다 왔다, 정말 무겁네
What could possibly be in there?
이 안에 뭐가 있지?
Hurry up and carry the next load, part-timer!
아르바이트생 서둘러 다음 걸 날라
That guy really sounds like an idiot.
저 인간은 정말 무식한 것 같군
DOESN'T SOUND INTELLIGENT AT ALL
'전혀 배운 티가 안 남'
Is it just me, or are we doing all of this backwards?
나만 이상하게 여기는 거야? 아니면 일을 전부 거꾸로 하나?
The theory of relativity and warp navigation
상대성 이론과 워프 항법은
parallels the relationship between dark matter and black holes...
암흑물질과 블랙홀의 관계와 평행을 이루지
So, that means...
그러면 그 의미는...
What have I gotten myself into? This is bad. Really, really bad.
내가 무슨 짓을 한 거지? 이건 안 좋아, 아주 안 좋다
This one seems normal.
이 사람은 평범해 보인다
The giant mantis...
거대한 사마귀가...
He's coming to kill me!
날 죽이러 온다
Stop. Don't come near me!
오지 마, 가까이 오지 말라고!
Stay away!
저리 가!
Praying mantis...
사마귀...
Trust me! You won't like how I taste!
믿어 줘! 난 맛이 없어
The giant mantis...
거대한 사마귀다
Mantis...
사마귀...
Praying mantis!
사마귀!
Oh, no. Praying mantis...
안 돼, 사마귀야
I'm so tipsy.
너무 취했다
Hey, fallen angel.
어이, 타락한 천사!
Sushi's a rare delicacy for you, right?
초밥은 귀해서 못 먹어 봤지?
It's actually for Yurine,
사실은 유리네 건데
but I could feed you a couple pieces.
너한테 몇 개 줄 수 있지
LAYING ON TOP OF HER THROW UP.
'자기 구토물 위에 누움'
I'm beat.
너무 힘들다
It is nice that they pay in cash.
현금으로 줘서 다행이야
But I only got 3200 yen for eight straight hours of work.
하지만 8시간 내내 일하고 겨우 3,200엔 받았어
I'll spend 1000 yen for food and necessities
1,000엔으로 음식과 필수품을 사고
and put 2200 in my savings.
2,200엔은 저축해야지
I need to get some sleep in order to do this again tomorrow.
내일 또 일하려면 잠을 자야 해
My house!
내 집이!
You again?
또 너야?
After slaving all day,
온종일 노예처럼 일했는데
the devil destroys my home.
악마가 내 집을 파괴했다
Nobody's coming for me from Heaven.
천국에서 날 찾으러 아무도 오지 않을 거야
I'm...
난...
Whoa, a shooting star!
우와, 별똥별이다!
Dropkick on her! Yeah her! I’ll take you down again!
드롭킥을 날린다! 저 애야! 널 다시 무찌를 거다!
Hate you! Love doesn’t exist in this world
네가 싫어! 이 세상에 사랑이란 없어
Fear the dropkick! An Angel looks for her halo
드롭킥을 겁내라! 천사는 후광을 찾는다
As she starves to death!
굶어 죽어가면서 말이야
It’s a love and hate relationship,
이건 애증 관계야
can’t leave each other alone
서로를 가만히 두지 않지
Like a galaxy-bursting shooting star!
은하에서 터지는 유성처럼
Slowly, slowly, sneak up and DIE!
천천히, 살금살금 몰래 다가가서 죽인다!
Test my heart, don’t stop
내 마음을 떠봐 멈추지 말고
Let’s go! Dream on! No matter human, angel or devil
가자! 꿈꿔! 인간이건 천사건 악마건
We’re a happy family La la la
우리는 행복한 가족이다 랄랄라
Let me say, I love you!!
내가 말할게 난 널 사랑해!
When all is said and done
모든 것이 끝나면
I’m home! Welcome back, it’s hot pot tonight!
나 왔어! 어서 와, 오늘 밤은 스키야키다!
Come, gather everyone! Let’s enjoy this meal!
모두 어서 모여! 이 요리를 즐기자!
For another crazy tomorrow
내일은 또 정신없을 거야
What next? What next? In the end, Wakeup!
뭔데? 또 뭐지? 결국 깨어나!
Gospel echoes.
복음이 메아리친다
Jacob's ladder comes down from the cloudy sky.
야곱의 사다리가 구름 낀 하늘에서 내려온다
New angel decend from above with the light.
저 높은 곳에서 새 천사가 빛과 함께 내려온다
Dropkick on My Devil!
사신짱 드롭킥! 다음 화에서도 여러분 마음에 샤이닝 위저드 기술을 겁니다!